Am I the asshole for not cooking with my
food labs group?
I (17 male) am currently in a foods and
nutrition class at my high school.
Every Friday, we cook something.
I often do the bare minimum with my team
to at least seem like a decent human
being, but the truth is, I have horrible
social anxiety with people I barely know.
I think differently, too; my brain
notices things, and I often question them
a lot forcefully.
This is because I was diagnosed with
autism when I was younger, so my brain
functions somewhat differently, and I
tend to also be more sensitive to sounds.
I often pace around the kitchen in class,
figuring out what comes next, cracking my
knuckles or tapping my fingers as a way
of stimming.
Two weeks ago, my dog unfortunately
passed away, and I took a break from
school for about two days, returning on
Friday.
I opted out of cooking because my
headspace was not good at all.
The next week, I felt ill; my head was
hurting, so I took a break again.
You can probably guess what happened
next, but I did not show up last week; I
got sick and needed antibiotics.
In fact, my entire family was sick and
still is.
I am going back tomorrow, on Monday, and
I am scared they will think I left them
to do all the work, that I am a
freeloader of some sort.
We also had an ingredient list-type
summative that we had to do, and my group
never did it.
The teacher said if we did not do it, we
need to bring in our own ingredients to
make the meal instead of her buying them.
So, I am kind of in trouble now.
I do not have a job either, so... yeah.
Anyway, that is all my talk.