Am I the asshole for not wanting to
attend my older sister's baby shower?
My older sister and her husband are
excited to welcome a baby girl in January.
We will be celebrating with family and
friends at their baby shower on October
11th.
Now, I will be honest, I, a 31 male, do
not like baby showers.
My family does not seem to get that.
It feels like they are begging me to go,
but I really do not want to.
I am not big on family gatherings either.
I understand some people might be upset
if I do not show up, but I cannot live my
life trying to please everyone.
I am more of a recluse and enjoy being
alone.
I can support in other ways.
What do you guys think?